It is time for prayer.
The SCOAN Mass Prayer
Tell your neighbor: "My heart knows that the case is settled."
If the case is settled,
it means that you are healed.
Say: "I am healed!"
"I am delivered!"
"I am blessed!"
"My heart knows that the case is settled."
The SCOAN Mass Prayer
Right now before we open our lips, begin to give thanks to God for your healing.
Give thanks to God for your deliverance.
Give thanks to Him for your blessing.
The SCOAN Mass Prayer
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
Amen.
Whatever situation you are facing, the root is demon.
I say, whatever situation you are facing, demon is the cause.
Are you ready?
So right now, the Lord wants to deliver you from this demon.
Right now open your lips.
Right now! Right now!
You demon, my body is the temple of Holy Ghost.
Right now open your lips and rebuke that demon in your life.
Rebuke it! Rebuke it!
The SCOAN Mass Prayer
In the name of Jesus!
In the mighty name of Jesus!
I rebuke that demon in your life!
That spirit that causes you lust.
Be rebuked, in the name of Jesus!
The SCOAN Mass Prayer
Whatever spirit that causes you destruction,
say: "You spirit, I curse you, in the name of Jesus!"
Be cursed!
In the name of Jesus!
The SCOAN Mass Prayer
Whatever is occupying your conscience, your heart, I declare you free, in the name of Jesus!
I say - be opened!
Be opened for the Holy Spirit!
Say: "Holy Spirit!"
Holy Spirit!
Say: "Whatever is occupying my body, my spirit, my soul - I declare you out!"
Out!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
The SCOAN Mass Prayer
Whatever chain demon might have used to connect you to himself -
it could be chain of poverty, chain of sickness, chain of disease,
chain of affliction, chain of infirmity -
begin to break it! Break it!
Break the chain!
In the mighty name of Jesus!
The SCOAN Mass Prayer
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
I break whatever chain satan is using to connect you.
Be broken!
That your situation is chain.
You are disconnected!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
In the name of Jesus, I command that disease,
that affliction,
that disease!
Right now cover yourself with the blood of Jesus.
Cover yourself with the blood of Jesus.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Give thanks to God.
The SCOAN Mass Prayer
Give thanks to God. Give thanks to Him.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up to date with the latest prophesies, deliverances, sermons and testimonies
from the Synagogue Church Of All Nations.
Emmanuel TV - Changing lives, Changing nations and Changing the world
TT: Reverend Daniel Yeboah
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 20/06/2018